Wow, that is way too generous.
يا إلهي، هذا سخاء مفرط.
Looks like
يبدو أن
your reaction was what was way too generous.
كان رد فعلك هو ما كان كريماً للغاية.
Look at you.
انظر إليك.
Cash would be tacky, right?
سيكون استخدام النقود أمراً غير لائق، أليس كذلك؟
But a pen...
لكن قلمًا...
You can write with it.
يمكنك الكتابة به.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
By the way, director.
بالمناسبة، يا مخرج.
How long are you staying?
إلى متى أنت مقيم؟
Call me Mr. Ding.
نادني السيد دينغ.
I quit.
لقد استقلت.
I'm setting up my own lab,
أقوم بتجهيز مختبري الخاص،
start my own business.
أبدأ مشروعي الخاص.
I'm here, in part,
أنا هنا، جزئياً،
to invite you to join my project.
أدعوكم للانضمام إلى مشروعي.
I heard it from Gu...
سمعت ذلك من غو...
No,
لا،
from Xie.
من شيه.
So you knew already.
إذن كنت تعرف ذلك بالفعل.
Xie
شي
told me about hiding his identity.
أخبرني عن إخفاء هويته.
He also said
وقال أيضاً
you're working on a drug to eliminate Affinity.
أنت تعمل على تطوير دواء للقضاء على الألفة.
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
My lab plans to take this on as well.
يخطط مختبري للقيام بهذا الأمر أيضاً.
Back at Genus,
بالعودة إلى جينوس،
I found out something classified.
لقد اكتشفت شيئاً سرياً.
Thirteen years ago,
قبل ثلاثة عشر عاماً،
a couple, both professors,
زوجان، كلاهما أستاذان جامعيان،
developed a cure to Affinity.
تم تطوير علاج لمرض التقارب.
But
لكن
something went wrong in the final stage.
حدث خطأ ما في المرحلة النهائية.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
No one knows.
لا أحد يعلم.
All that's known is
كل ما هو معروف هو
their notes
ملاحظاتهم
were sealed in a glass drive,
كانت محكمة الإغلاق داخل محرك أقراص زجاجي،
split into three pieces.
مقسمة إلى ثلاثة أجزاء.
The first
الأول
is in Sunset Creek Town.
تقع في بلدة صن سيت كريك.
Sunset Creek Town?
بلدة سانست كريك؟
Isn't that where you're headed?
أليس هذا هو المكان الذي تتجه إليه؟
That place is dangerous.
ذلك المكان خطير.
I won't take you.
لن آخذك.
Your brother wouldn't allow it either.
أخوك لن يسمح بذلك أيضاً.
You're strong in a fight.
أنت قوي في القتال.
Of course you'd protect me.
بالطبع ستحميني.
I'll talk to my brother when I get back.
سأتحدث مع أخي عندما أعود.
and have him add me to the mission.
واطلب منه أن يضيفني إلى المهمة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Thanks, Mr. Ding.
شكراً لك يا سيد دينغ.
I'll head out.
سأغادر.
Why pull her into
لماذا تجرها إلى ذلك؟
the fragment search?
البحث عن الأجزاء؟
The Special Administration Bureau is also after those fragments.
يسعى مكتب الإدارة الخاصة أيضاً إلى الحصول على تلك الشظايا.
Bringing her in
إحضارها
helps us get more leads from their side.
يساعدنا ذلك في الحصول على المزيد من العملاء المحتملين من جانبهم.
And if you go berserk,
وإذا جن جنونك،
having an Yin nearby is safer.
وجود يين في الجوار أكثر أماناً.
Before making any decisions,
قبل اتخاذ أي قرارات،
you need to consult me.
عليك استشارتي.
It's too dangerous. You're not going.
الأمر خطير للغاية. لن تذهب.
That's exactly why I have to go.
لهذا السبب تحديداً عليّ الذهاب.
What if Xie Xinxu goes berserk?
ماذا لو أصيبت شي شينكسو بالجنون؟
I can calm him.
أستطيع تهدئته.
An inhibitor shot will also do.
كما أن حقنة مثبطة ستفي بالغرض أيضاً.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
After forming a pact,
بعد إبرام الاتفاق،
a Ren becomes psychologically dependent on an Yin.
يصبح الرين معتمداً نفسياً على الين.
What if Xie Xinxu
ماذا لو شيه شينكسو
develops separation anxiety?
هل يُصاب بقلق الانفصال؟
That would affect the mission.
سيؤثر ذلك على المهمة.
Then have Li Xiang and Lin Juan go with you.
ثم اطلب من لي شيانغ ولين جوان أن يذهبا معك.
They can protect you.
بإمكانهم حمايتك.
Li Xiang?
لي شيانغ؟
Is it that pretty young lady
هل هي تلك الشابة الجميلة؟
you often work with?
مع من تعمل غالباً؟
Did you form a pact in private?
هل أبرمتم اتفاقاً سراً؟
Who told you anything?
من أخبرك بأي شيء؟
Three years ago, when you were twenty-five,
قبل ثلاث سنوات، عندما كنت في الخامسة والعشرين من عمرك،
you were sick for a long time.
لقد كنت مريضاً لفترة طويلة.
You said it was exhaustion,
قلتَ إنه الإرهاق،
but it was your virus going berserk
لكن فيروسك هو الذي خرج عن السيطرة
and nearly killed you, didn't it?
وكادت أن تقتلك، أليس كذلك؟
You must have formed a pact with a Ren
لا بد أنك أبرمت اتفاقاً مع رين
to survive.
للبقاء على قيد الحياة.
Right?
يمين؟
That's not your concern.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Enough.
كافٍ.
It's late.
إنه متأخر.
You should head back.
يجب عليك العودة.
I'll walk you out.
سأرافقك إلى الخارج.
No need. Someone's picking me up.
لا داعي لذلك. سيأتي أحدهم ليأخذني.
It's swollen.
إنه متورم.
So careless.
إهمالٌ شديد.
Cold-blooded.
بارد الدم.
I'm off, Siyuan.
أنا ذاهب يا سيوان.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
Careful.
انتبه.
Mr. Wu, you didn't need to rush discharge.
سيد وو، لم يكن هناك داعٍ للتعجل في خروج المريض.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Have you found a suitable Ren?
هل وجدت رين مناسبة؟
We selected all female Ren
اخترنا جميع الإناث من رين
carrying a high-activity Affinity B virus.
حامل لفيروس من النوع B عالي النشاط.
After forming a pact with you,
بعد إبرام اتفاق معك،
they should help you recover quickly.
سيساعدونك على التعافي بسرعة.
Who are you acting superior for all day?
لمن تتصرف بتعالٍ طوال اليوم؟
A Ren who can't work with a team (Watch on www.kisskh,la or www.kisskh,id to support admin)
رين الذي لا يستطيع العمل ضمن فريق (شاهد على www.kisskh.la أو www.kisskh.id لدعم الإدارة)
is only fit to be a punching bag.
لا يصلح إلا أن يكون كيس ملاكمة.
Hey.
يا.
I'm talking to you.
أنا أتحدث إليك.
Didn't you hear me?
ألم تسمعني؟
Are you dead or what?
هل أنت ميت أم ماذا؟
Say something.
قل شيئا.
♪Wrote the story's end♪
♪كتبتُ نهاية القصة♪
♪But wrote it in the sand♪
♪لكنها كُتبت على الرمال♪
You clutch that junk all day.
أنت تتمسك بتلك الأشياء طوال اليوم.
Let go!
اتركه!
Let go of me!
اتركني!
Release me!
أطلق سراحي!
♪Stick to the story please♪
♪التزم بالقصة من فضلك♪
♪You say that you want to see me♪
♪تقول إنك تريد رؤيتي♪
♪But truth is scary, so here♪
♪لكن الحقيقة مخيفة، لذا ها هي♪
♪I stand alone♪
♪أنا أقف وحيداً♪
♪Alone♪
♪وحيدًا♪
♪You say that you want to know me♪
♪تقول إنك تريد أن تعرفني♪
♪Now you have all of me♪
♪الآن أنت تملكني بالكامل♪
♪And I am alone♪
♪وأنا وحيد♪
♪Alone♪
♪وحيدًا♪
Run a check on her name.
تحقق من اسمها.
Her name is Li Xiang.
اسمها لي شيانغ.
She's among the selected Ren.
إنها من بين المختارين من رين.
Bring her in.
أدخلوها.
I can form a pact with you,
يمكنني عقد اتفاق معك،
as your blood supply.
مثل إمداد الدم الخاص بك.
But you must transfer me to your side.
لكن يجب عليك نقلي إلى جانبك.
I never want to go back.
لا أريد العودة أبداً.
You want to negotiate?
هل تريد التفاوض؟
Prove your value first.
أثبت قيمتك أولاً.
♪It tastes like hell, and she's the one♪
طعمها كريه للغاية، وهي الوحيدة المناسبة.
♪I see inferno, can't get enough♪
♪أرى الجحيم، لا أكتفي منه♪
♪Burning city, fiery love♪
♪مدينة تحترق، حب ملتهب♪
♪It's a fervor, not a crush♪
♪إنه شغف، وليس مجرد إعجاب♪
If you don't want it, forget it.
إذا كنت لا تريده، فانساه.
So I can leave the Administration Bureau today?
هل يمكنني مغادرة مكتب الإدارة اليوم؟
These are my rules.
هذه هي قواعدي.
In front of me,
أمامي،
(Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
your mind
عقلك
can hold nothing but me.
لا يمكن أن يحتوي على شيء سواي.
If you can't,
إذا لم تستطع،
you can leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Sheath your claws.
أغمد مخالبك.
I'll let it slide once.
سأتغاضى عن الأمر هذه المرة.
There won't be a second time.
لن يكون هناك مرة ثانية.
This place is yours now.
هذا المكان ملكك الآن.
I'll come by regularly.
سأزوركم بانتظام.
[Xiang]
[شيانغ]
Lin Juan and I are ready.
أنا ولين جوان مستعدان.
We are leaving for Sunset Creek Town the day after tomorrow.
سنغادر إلى بلدة سانست كريك بعد غد.
Nongyu is going with you.
نونغيو سيذهب معك.
Be careful out there.
كن حذراً هناك.
You must keep her safe.
يجب عليك حمايتها.
Why bring her all of a sudden?
لماذا أحضرتها فجأة؟
She cares about Xie Xinxu more than I thought.
إنها تهتم بشي شينشو أكثر مما كنت أعتقد.
If she doesn't see his disappearance for herself,
إذا لم تلاحظ اختفاءه بنفسها،
she won't let it go.
لن تتخلى عن الأمر.
I understand.
أفهم.
Coming by tonight?
هل ستمرّ الليلة؟
If you don't suppress the virus these days,
إذا لم تقم بكبح جماح الفيروس هذه الأيام،
you'll get hurt easily.
ستتعرض للأذى بسهولة.
It's swollen.
إنه متورم.
An Yin bonded to a Ren
ارتبط الين بـ رين
should be physically stronger.
ينبغي أن يكون أقوى بدنياً.
There's no way she'd be weaker than before.
لا يمكن بأي حال من الأحوال أن تكون أضعف مما كانت عليه من قبل.
I'll come tomorrow. That's it.
سآتي غداً. هذا كل شيء.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
What happened to your arm?
ماذا حدث لذراعك؟
Nothing. I bumped it yesterday.
لا شيء. لقد صدمته أمس.
You've always been
لطالما كنت
a bad liar, since we were kids.
كاذب سيء، منذ أن كنا صغاراً.
Don't tell me
لا تخبرني
you never formed a pact with Xie Xinxu,
لم تُبرم أي اتفاق مع شي شينشو،
and that's why you're this fragile.
ولهذا السبب أنت بهذه الهشاشة.
I...
أنا...
Then I can tell you right now
إذن يمكنني أن أخبرك الآن
the real reason Xie Xinxu got close to you.
السبب الحقيقي وراء تقرب شي شينشو منك.
What you did to Nongyu,
ما فعلته بنونغيو،
I'll give you a chance.
سأمنحك فرصة.
Say it yourself.
قلها بنفسك.
My arm was injured.
أُصيبت ذراعي.
My brother misunderstood it.
لقد أساء أخي فهم الأمر.
Come up with an explanation.
قدم تفسيراً.
This is on me.
هذا خطأي.
I wasn't careful last night.
لم أكن حذراً الليلة الماضية.
It won't happen again.
لن يتكرر ذلك.
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Alright. I'll stop.
حسناً، سأتوقف.
I'm making her shy.
أنا أجعلها خجولة.
♪Tie a rope on my throat♪
♪اربط حبلاً حول عنقي♪
♪Till I start to choke♪
♪حتى أبدأ بالاختناق♪
You're heading to Sunset Creek Town the day after tomorrow.
ستتوجه إلى بلدة سانست كريك بعد غد.
And before that,
وقبل ذلك،
you better rein it in.
من الأفضل أن تكبح جماح نفسك.
Siyuan!
سيوان!
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
Call me every day so I know you're safe.
اتصل بي كل يوم لأطمئن عليك.
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
No need to walk me out.
لا داعي لمرافقتي إلى الخارج.
♪The lies we told hold me still♪
♪الأكاذيب التي قلناها تُبقيني ساكناً♪
♪Chasing shadows but I am standing still♪
♪أطارد الأوهام لكنني واقفٌ في مكاني♪
Starting tonight, you'll sleep in the spare room,
ابتداءً من الليلة، ستنام في الغرفة الإضافية.
given what happened last night.
بالنظر إلى ما حدث الليلة الماضية.
Good night.
طاب مساؤك.
It seems Sunset Creek Town has only one place to eat.
يبدو أن بلدة سانست كريك لا يوجد بها سوى مكان واحد لتناول الطعام.
It's about an eight-hour drive.
تستغرق الرحلة بالسيارة حوالي ثماني ساعات.
Let's split the driving. You take half, I'll take half.
لنتقاسم القيادة. أنت تأخذ النصف، وأنا آخذ النصف الآخر.
Let's head out.
هيا بنا ننطلق.
[Sunset Town]
[مدينة الغروب]
[DINER]
[مطعم]
Why didn't you wake me up?
لماذا لم توقظني؟
You drove the whole way yourself.
لقد قدت السيارة طوال الطريق بنفسك.
With shifts,
مع نوبات العمل،
it would be eight hours.
ستستغرق ثماني ساعات.
Alone, I make it six.
بمفردي، يصبح العدد ستة.
You just think I drive too slow.
أنت تعتقد فقط أنني أقود ببطء شديد.
My stomach hurts.
معدتي تؤلمني.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
[Ding]
[دينغ]
Hello, Mr. Ding.
مرحباً، سيد دينغ.
Xu.
شو.
I put a bottle of medicine in your bag.
لقد وضعت زجاجة دواء في حقيبتك.
It regulates the neurotransmitters in your brain
فهو ينظم النواقل العصبية في دماغك
to simulate emotions.
لمحاكاة المشاعر.
One in the morning, one at night.
واحدة في الصباح، وواحدة في الليل.
[Emotion Emotional Supplement] But
[مكمل عاطفي] لكن
try not to expect too much.
حاول ألا تتوقع الكثير.
Alright, I understand.
حسناً، فهمت.
The restroom here is surprisingly clean.
دورة المياه هنا نظيفة بشكل مدهش.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Wait for the right moment
انتظر اللحظة المناسبة
to take Xie Xinxu down.
لإسقاط Xie Xinxu.
Steer clear of a head-on conflict.
تجنب المواجهة المباشرة.
You can't win head-on anyway.
لا يمكنك الفوز في المواجهة المباشرة على أي حال.
Yeah.
نعم.
I'll follow your plan.
سأتبع خطتك.
After all, you won't let Wu Siyuan down.
في النهاية، لن تخذل وو سييوان.
Your iced lemonade, miss.
عصير الليمون المثلج الخاص بكِ يا آنسة.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Just back from the restroom,
عدتُ للتو من دورة المياه،
and already on cold drinks?
ويتناولون المشروبات الباردة بالفعل؟
Check, please.
تحقق من فضلك.
[Sunset Creek Tavern, Total: 34344]
[حانة صن سيت كريك، المجموع: 34344]
Hold on a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
Go wait in the car first.
انتظر في السيارة أولاً.
I'll be right out.
سأخرج فوراً.
Why?
لماذا؟
Because I have no plans to pay.
لأنني لا أنوي الدفع.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪